

Faruk Ozgu

Jr. Developer

Career Path

I am aiming for a career as Front End Developer and UI-UX Designer. I have knowledge of Front End Development. I am experienced in HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap and Javascript languages. I have experience and knowledge of operating systems.

Education

Information Security Technology 2020 - 2022

Dogus University - Istanbul

Information Technologies 2015 - 2019

Uskudar Vocational and Technical High School - Istanbul

Certificates

Erasmus+ Mobile Application Development Internship

Szent György Media and Informatics Vocational High School Hungary / Budapest - 2018

Beginner Front End Development Path

Patika | 2022

HTML5, CSS3 & Javascript 101

Turkcell | 2022

UI-UX Design with Adobe XD

BTK Academy | 2022

Work Experience

I.T Intern

BDP International | March 2022- June 2022

New computer and operating system installations, providing domain accounts entry and providing technical support to personnel.

I.T Intern

Colakoglu Metallurgy | September 2018 - June 2019

New computer and operating system installations, providing domain accounts entry and providing technical support to personnel.

Skills

- HTML5 & CSS3
- Bootstrap
- Javascript
- os
- Adobe XD

Contact

- E-mail: faruk.ozgufb@gmail.com
- · Portfolio: www.farukozgu.com
- · Linkedin: farukozgu